{
    "source": "C:/Users/Jonathan/source/repos/Python/Day 31/data/Top 100 Kanji .csv",
    "questionHeading": "Kanji",
    "answerHeading": "Meaning",
    "models": [
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u65e5",
                "answerText": "day, sun, Japan, counter for days"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715140665.399572,
            "interval": 9
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e00",
                "answerText": "one"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715140676.890486,
            "interval": 9
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u56fd",
                "answerText": "country"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715140736.0819573,
            "interval": 5
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4f1a",
                "answerText": "meeting; meet"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715140739.4860065,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4eba",
                "answerText": "person"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715140743.5935462,
            "interval": 5
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5e74",
                "answerText": "year, counter for years"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115974.3135269,
            "interval": 0
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5927",
                "answerText": "large, big"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715169471.6428926,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5341",
                "answerText": "ten, 10"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715169461.6779506,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e8c",
                "answerText": "two, 2"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115988.39553,
            "interval": 0
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u672c",
                "answerText": "book, present, true, counter for long cylindrical things"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715169445.1982481,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e2d",
                "answerText": "in, inside, middle, mean, center"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u9577",
                "answerText": "long, leader, superior, senior"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138160.2942865,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u51fa",
                "answerText": "exit, leave, go out"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138164.6651402,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e09",
                "answerText": "three, 3"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u540c",
                "answerText": "same, agree, equal"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6642",
                "answerText": "time, hour"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715169507.8379908,
            "interval": 0
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u653f",
                "answerText": "politics, government"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e8b",
                "answerText": "matter, thing, fact, business, reason, possibly"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138191.4464064,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u81ea",
                "answerText": "oneself"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u884c",
                "answerText": "going, journey, carry out, line, row"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u793e",
                "answerText": "company, firm, office, association, shrine"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u898b",
                "answerText": "see, hopes, chances, idea, opinion, look at, visible"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138211.91801,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6708",
                "answerText": "month, moon"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5206",
                "answerText": "part, minute of time, understand"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u8b70",
                "answerText": "deliberation, consultation, debate"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138224.9668407,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5f8c",
                "answerText": "behind, back, later"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u524d",
                "answerText": "in front, before"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138232.954704,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6c11",
                "answerText": "people, nation, subjects"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u751f",
                "answerText": "life, genuine, birth"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138241.564942,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u9023",
                "answerText": "take along, lead, join, connect"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e94",
                "answerText": "five, 5"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u767a",
                "answerText": "departure, discharge, emit, start from"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138254.8365197,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u9593",
                "answerText": "interval, space"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -2
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5bfe",
                "answerText": "opposite, even, equal, versus, anti-, compare"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e0a",
                "answerText": "above, up"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138268.6891446,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u90e8",
                "answerText": "section, bureau, dept, class, copy, part, portion"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138272.6506753,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6771",
                "answerText": "east"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u8005",
                "answerText": "someone, person"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u515a",
                "answerText": "party, faction, clique"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5730",
                "answerText": "ground, earth"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5408",
                "answerText": "fit, suit, join, 0.1"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5e02",
                "answerText": "market, city, town"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u696d",
                "answerText": "business, vocation, arts, performance"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5185",
                "answerText": "inside, within, between, among, house, home"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u76f8",
                "answerText": "inter-, mutual, together, each other, minister of state"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u65b9",
                "answerText": "direction, person, alternative"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u56db",
                "answerText": "four, 4"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5b9a",
                "answerText": "determine, fix, establish, decide"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4eca",
                "answerText": "now; the present"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u56de",
                "answerText": "-times, round, revolve, counter"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u65b0",
                "answerText": "new"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138341.6313615,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5834",
                "answerText": "location, place"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u91d1",
                "answerText": "gold"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138352.3911583,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u54e1",
                "answerText": "employee, member, number, the one in charge"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e5d",
                "answerText": "nine, 9"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5165",
                "answerText": "enter, insert"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138364.7445052,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u9078",
                "answerText": "elect, select, choose, prefer"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u7acb",
                "answerText": "stand up, rise"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u958b",
                "answerText": "open, unfold, unseal"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u624b",
                "answerText": "hand"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u7c73",
                "answerText": "rice, USA, meter"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u529b",
                "answerText": "power, strength, strong, strain, bear up, exert"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5b66",
                "answerText": "study, learning, science"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u554f",
                "answerText": "question, ask, problem"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u9ad8",
                "answerText": "tall, high, expensive"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4ee3",
                "answerText": "substitute, change, convert, replace, period"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u660e",
                "answerText": "bright, light"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -2
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5b9f",
                "answerText": "reality, truth"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5186",
                "answerText": "circle, yen, round"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u95a2",
                "answerText": "connection, barrier, gateway, involve, concerning"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6c7a",
                "answerText": "decide, fix, agree upon, appoint"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5b50",
                "answerText": "child"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138449.3138692,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u52d5",
                "answerText": "move, motion, change"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4eac",
                "answerText": "capital"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5168",
                "answerText": "whole, entire, all, complete, fulfill"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u76ee",
                "answerText": "eye, class, look, insight, experience"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u8868",
                "answerText": "surface, table, chart, diagram"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138473.6507418,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6226",
                "answerText": "war, battle, match"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u7d4c",
                "answerText": "longitude, pass thru, expire, warp"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u901a",
                "answerText": "traffic, pass through, avenue, commute"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5916",
                "answerText": "outside"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -2
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6700",
                "answerText": "utmost, most, extreme"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -2
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u8a00",
                "answerText": "say, word"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138512.866631,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6c0f",
                "answerText": "family name, surname, clan"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u73fe",
                "answerText": "present, existing, actual"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138521.9033659,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u7406",
                "answerText": "logic, arrangement, reason, justice, truth"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138526.5755823,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u8abf",
                "answerText": "tune, tone, meter, prepare, investigate"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4f53",
                "answerText": "body, substance, object, reality"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5316",
                "answerText": "change, take the form of, influence, enchant, delude, -ization"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -2
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u7530",
                "answerText": "rice field, rice paddy"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u5f53",
                "answerText": "hit, right, appropriate"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138551.3225572,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u516b",
                "answerText": "eight, 8"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138554.8154616,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u516d",
                "answerText": "six, 6"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138559.2705033,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u7d04",
                "answerText": "promise, approximately, shrink"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138563.043065,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e3b",
                "answerText": "lord, chief, master, main thing, principal"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138566.5064669,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u984c",
                "answerText": "topic, subject"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138570.4635913,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u4e0b",
                "answerText": "below, down, descend, give, low, inferior"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715115020.7581997,
            "interval": -1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u9996",
                "answerText": "neck"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138578.3767562,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u610f",
                "answerText": "idea, mind, heart, taste, thought"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138582.6705706,
            "interval": 1
        },
        {
            "flashCard": {
                "questionText": "\u6cd5",
                "answerText": "method, law, rule, principle, model, system"
            },
            "mostRecentCorrectAnswer": 1715138586.069233,
            "interval": 1
        }
    ],
    "indices": [
        81,
        32,
        66,
        88,
        80,
        77,
        73,
        37,
        22,
        65,
        78,
        63,
        59,
        45,
        56,
        6,
        53,
        72,
        39,
        33,
        57,
        41,
        14,
        54,
        48,
        23,
        58,
        40,
        30,
        86,
        25,
        87,
        38,
        64,
        69,
        42,
        27,
        74,
        70,
        16,
        47,
        51,
        36,
        83,
        49,
        19,
        96,
        9,
        7,
        43,
        79,
        29,
        44,
        20,
        60,
        61,
        18,
        67,
        10,
        68,
        46,
        62,
        13,
        89,
        75,
        82,
        55,
        8,
        90,
        31,
        34,
        17,
        5,
        28,
        91,
        71,
        15,
        98,
        3,
        35,
        84,
        92,
        97,
        99,
        21,
        11,
        76,
        26,
        93,
        52,
        24,
        85,
        12,
        95,
        50,
        94,
        4,
        2,
        1,
        0
    ],
    "currentIndex": 0
}